Davy SEBBAH

Full Stack Developer

Tel Aviv | 053-864-0333 | d.sebbah@yahoo.fr Github LinkedIn | Portfolio

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in JavaScript based programming. Possess strong skills in adaptation and determination. I am drawn to logic, to creation. I am organized and methodical. I seek to constantly evolve towards the mastery and the realization of more and more elaborate projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, DOM AJAX: HTTP/XML + JSON, Database: SQL + MongoDB Node.js, Express, JsonWebToken, Bcrypt, React-Redux

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Social Network - Github | Screenshot | Demo

Small social network allowing to send posts, images, videos, to comment on the submissions of each one, like or unlike. There is a registration form with password encryption. Everything is recorded in a database.

Tokens - LocalStorage - Node.js - Express - JSON - CRUD - MongoDB- React -Redux

Site e-Commerce - Github | Screenshot

As part of a draft e-commerce site, I am asked to create a responsive site that allows to display the products for sale, to obtain details on a selected product, to fill out a contact form and to confirm procurement.

HTML - CSS - Javascript Vanilla - API REST

EXPERIENCE

Manager Jerusalem SOS-Photovoltaïque 06/2020 - 03/2021

- Supervision of 22 employees Defined precisely the objectives then observed and the human and material resources to achieve them.
- Restructuring and reorganization of missions and roles Optimization and Profiling

Madrich Haifa Yemin Ord 10/2018 - 07/2019

- Weekly meetings and follow up with trouble teens background by giving them council, advice and resources to overcome their situation.
- Know how to take into account the context of life, the sensitivity of the other, target their needs, listen actively and propose a new way to help them

National Police France Interior Ministry 2002 - 2017

- Supervision of 20 staff members Gave directions, be exemplary, organized a work plan, managed tensions
- Intervention on public roads Tooke decisions and Keep cool
- Escort of detainees and presentation to magistrates Respect and not preconception

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development JavaScript program

10/2021 - 12/2021

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Tel Aviv

Web Developer Full Stack

France

Openclassrooms e-line

03/2021 09/2021

LANGUAGES

English - fluent, Hebrew - fluent, French - native